cablemover.com 2014-03-26

# Privacy Policy | CableMover

## Enter your address to see special offers

## To see TV, Internet and Phone offers, enter your new address.

Address

Apt / Unit

ZIP Code

Email (For a reminder of your results. No spam, we promise.)

[submit](javascript: void\(0\);)

CableMover.com and associated web sites (the “Website”) is offered by sponsoring cable companies as listed on our home page (the “Cable Providers”) and is powered by CTAM Marketing Corp. ("we," "our" or "us"). This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy policy and security practices for this Website. We also work with third parties that provide services to you relating to moving and relocation, such as change of address, moving quotes and other related services (the “Service Providers”) This Website is specifically designed for persons who are 18 years of age or older.

**Information Collected About You**  
We collect information about you that is provided by you to us or a Cable Provider or Service Provider, such as your name, address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses and other information that can identify you as a specific individual ("Information"). On those pages of the Website where Information is collected in order for you to purchase or request further information about a product or service, we describe what information is required in order to provide you with the product, service or information that you have requested. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13. If a Service Provider requires a birth date to order a specific product or service, you may not be able to enter a birth date that indicates that you are less than 13 years old. We collect Information when you:

  * Become authorized to use the Website
  * Purchase a product or service
  * Request further information regarding a product or service
  * Disconnect a service
  * Contact us

**Links to Other Sites**  
This Website may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information, which may include, without limitation, when you leave our Website to complete surveys or click on advertisements that direct you to third party sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by this Website.

**Cookies**  
We do not track or collect information about your visits to other Internet sites. Certain technical information is automatically collected about your computer each time you request a page during a visit to this Website. This information may include your IP address, operating system and Internet browser software (e.g., Safari, Firefox, or Internet Explorer). We assign you a "cookie" (i.e., a tiny packet of identifying information passed between your browser and a Web site) each time you visit this site. You do not provide this information; it is collected automatically as a means for supporting your visit to this Website. This cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information. You can always choose to not receive a cookie file by enabling your browser to refuse cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie. Please be aware that by refusing to accept a cookie you will not be able to make optimal use of this site. We use third-party advertising technology to serve ads when you visit Web sites upon which we advertise. This technology uses information about your visits to Web sites upon which we advertise (not including your name, address or other personal information), to serve our ads to you. In the course of serving our advertisements to you, a unique third-party cookie may be placed or recognized on your browser. In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by our ad serving partner, to help manage our online advertising. These Web beacons enable our ad server to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site and to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable.

**Notifications and Promotions**  
Cable Providers and Service Providers that you select may use your e-mail address or telephone number to contact you in order to confirm or arrange service appointments, answer questions or provide requested information, or to resolve outstanding issues pertinent to the delivery of products or services ordered by you. Cable Providers and Service Providers may use your e-mail address or other contact information to send you notifications about new features, products, services, specials, service providers, promotions or other opportunities available through this site, or to confirm or improve customer service, and all collection of information through the Cable Provider or Service Provider is governed by their individual privacy policies.

**Our Service Providers**  
It is our intention to maintain reputable Service Providers to offer users a variety of products and services available through the Website. All services and products throughout the Website are provided by third parties and are identified and described as such. When choosing to purchase products or services from any Service Provider, you must take into consideration that you will be transacting business directly with this Service Provider. The information provided by you and collected by a Service Provider will be similar to information that would be provided pursuant to a purchase of such product or service by telephone or in person. Neither CTAM nor the Cable Providers are responsible for the quality of service rendered by Service Providers.

**Opt In Policy/Sharing Your Information**  
We will not sell, share or rent your Information in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement unless you specifically elect to make your Information available to third parties by checking the applicable opt in box or boxes located on the Website.

**Use of Your Information**  
Information collected on this site may be used to:

  * Facilitate your orders for services and products
  * Send notifications
  * Promote our service and other available services and products
  * Respond to your questions or suggestions
  * Improve the quality of the Website

**Responses to Your Questions or Suggestions**  
We will use your e-mail address or telephone number to respond when you submit a question or suggestion, or request assistance with using or accessing this Website.

**Cable Providers and other Service Providers**  
When you use the Website to enter your Information, we deliver that Information to a Cable Provider serving your address or area. You will then be taken to the Cable Provider’s site if you choose to order a service plan. You may also be given quotes for services by certain Service Providers. Our Cable Providers and Service Providers will require certain personally identifiable information about you, including applicable billing and payment information, in order to fulfill your purchase order or service initiations. When you purchase a product or service, you are contracting directly with the applicable Cable Provider or Service Provider offering the purchased product or service and we do not have access to that personally identifiable information. The applicable Cable Provider or Service Provider will be responsible for the fulfillment, delivery, billing, customer service, warranty and support of its own products and services. We recommend that you examine the privacy policies of all third parties from which you purchase products and services, whether through our Website, by telephone, in person or by other means, to understand their procedures for using and disclosing your personally identifiable information.

**Legal Obligations**  
If required by law, we may disclose information you have provided in connection with your use of this site or the purchase of products and services. We may also disclose information about someone who poses a threat to our interests (such as customer fraud) or whose activities could damage or bring harm to others.

**Notifications of Changes**  
We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. If we are going to use your Information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via e-mail or other available means. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your Information in this materially different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect Information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Website notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also e-mail users, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

**Contacting Us**  
If you need help using our service or have a question regarding the products or services offered by any of our service providers, email us at [info@ctam.com](mailto:info@ctam.com) or call us at 703-549-4200.
